ASHISH UPRETI

0450912133 • upretiashish133@gmail.com • Penshurst, NSW

CAREER OBJECTIVES:

Motivated and dedicated IT Support Specialist with sound knowledge and experience in providing helpdesk support services to end users, performing installation, assembly, disassembly, configuration, and maintenance of desktop computers, network devices, and servers, also familiar with general office duties. Can work independently and take ownership of tasks. I am also learning coding and web development to upskill myself, and I have used my technical skills in the best interest of both my team members and the company. I have worked in the real world, duties including team member to administrative.

KEY SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES:

- Experienced troubleshooting, ticketing system and resolving issues related to VPN, MFA, mobile phones, printers, Windows 10, and O365 application.
- Advanced skills in UI designs, HTML, CSS, VS code, Figma, Slack, JavaScript for Software, and front-end web development.
- Strong experience working with databases, web development and designing software's like WordPress, Wix, GitHub along with project management tools.
- Great experience in preparing effective, easy to read reports and dashboards
- > Excellent communication and verbal skills to help the client.
- Good experience using Microsoft 365 apps like; power automate flow, office word, PowerPoint, Excel.
- ➤ Co-operative personality, friendly, positive, and can-do attitude, always striving for gaining the most value to an organization from IT solution.
- Experienced troubleshooting and resolving issues related to VPN, MFA, mobile phones, printers, Windows 10, and O365 applications.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

03/2022 – 07/2022 (Internship)

IT Support and Helpdesk at Nick Mascitelli Imports

- Provided remote and onsite technical support for employees, including software and hardware issues.
- Implemented new technologies to improve the efficiency of the support process.
- Resolved complex technical issues in a timely and effective manner.
- Maintained accurate and updated records of all incidents and solutions.
- Performing tests and evaluations of new software and hardware.
- Produce timely and detailed service reports
- Establishing good relationships with all Stakeholders.
- Documentation, office administration and management under supervision of manager.
- Creating tickets for the issues faced by clients to solve their problems accordingly.

03/2021 - Current

Restaurant Manager at Oporto

- Recruiting and interviewing new staffs.
- Preparing weekly rosters using Adi-insight.
- Preparing weekly purchase summary report with excel and Macromatix software.
- Handling complaints and organizing the team.
- Monitor the performance of sales devices and software.
- Dealing with customer queries and complaint.
- Train employees, inspire them to better serve the customers.

EDUCATION:

o Bachelor of, Information and Technology

Federation University at MIT & Kings Own Institute

- Coding Bootcamp Front-End Development, November 2022
 - Dented Code Academy Sydney, NSW
- Professional Year(2023-Current)

Queensland International Business Academy, Sydney Campus, NSW.

REFERENCES:

Available upon request